christiansonline.com.au 2019-03-04

# Privacy Policy | Christian Dating, Christian Singles Dating, Online Dating Australia

ChristiansOnline.com.au was founded on the idea that Australia needed an online Christian Community, to bring together people with a common belief to pray for world issues, make new Christian friends and find anything you may need as a Christian person. We understand that your right to privacy is of the utmost importance. To that end, we are committed to the protection of your personal information. Any information we collect from you is used only to fulfil your needs. Our privacy policy appears below in detail. Please note by visiting ChristiansOnline.com.au, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

**What if I contact you?**

We may keep a copy of any correspondence from you.

**Who Do You Share Information With?**

We do not sell, trade or rent user information to anyone.

ChristiansOnline.com.au operates its own customer service department. Unlike other online businesses, when you become a member or sign up for Christian Singles, your details never leave ChristiansOnline.com.au.

**Under What Circumstances Will You Contact Me?**

You will receive an email confirming your membership and the occasional Newsletter, advising you of what new sections have been launched on ChristiansOnline.com.au.

If your membership form does not contain enough information (eg: Login Name) for us to complete it, one of our customer service representatives will contact you via email.

**What About Cookies?**

Currently ChristiansOnline.com.au does not use cookies.

Please note that other sites with links to ChristiansOnline.com.au (eg. sites we advertise with) may use cookies and may collect additional information about you. We are not responsible for the information policies of these sites and users may wish to acquaint themselves with the privacy policies of those other sites.

Our business success depends on our discretion and our understanding of the importance of your privacy. If you have suggestions for enhancing our privacy policy, please contact ChristiansOnline.com.au directly.
